[
  {
    "Question": "Maine",
    "Answer": "Augusta"
  },
  {
    "Question": "New Hampshire",
    "Answer": "Concord"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Vermont",
    "Answer": "Montpelier"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Massachusetts",
    "Answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rhode Island",
    "Answer": "Providence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Connecticut",
    "Answer": "Hartford"
  },
  {
    "Question": "New York",
    "Answer": "Albany"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Pennsylvania",
    "Answer": "Harrisburg"
  },
  {
    "Question": "New Jersey",
    "Answer": "Trenton"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Delaware",
    "Answer": "Dover"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Maryland",
    "Answer": "Annapolis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "West Virginia",
    "Answer": "Charleston"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Virginia",
    "Answer": "Richmond"
  },
  {
    "Question": "North Carolina",
    "Answer": "Raleigh"
  },
  {
    "Question": "South Carolina",
    "Answer": "Columbia"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Georgia",
    "Answer": "Atlanta"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Florida",
    "Answer": "Tallahassee"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Alabama",
    "Answer": "Montgomery"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mississippi",
    "Answer": "Jackson"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Louisiana",
    "Answer": "Baton Rouge"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Arkansas",
    "Answer": "Little Rock"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tennessee",
    "Answer": "Nashville"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kentucky",
    "Answer": "Frankfort"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ohio",
    "Answer": "Columbus"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Indiana",
    "Answer": "Indianapolis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Michigan",
    "Answer": "Lansing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Illinois",
    "Answer": "Springfield"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Wisconsin",
    "Answer": "Madison"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Minnesota",
    "Answer": "St. Paul"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Iowa",
    "Answer": "Des Moines"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Missouri",
    "Answer": "Jefferson City"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Texas",
    "Answer": "Austin"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Oklahoma",
    "Answer": "Oklahoma City"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kansas",
    "Answer": "Topeka"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nebraska",
    "Answer": "Lincoln"
  },
  {
    "Question": "South Dakota",
    "Answer": "Pierre"
  },
  {
    "Question": "North Dakota",
    "Answer": "Bismarck"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Montana",
    "Answer": "Helena"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Wyoming",
    "Answer": "Cheyenne"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Colorado",
    "Answer": "Denver"
  },
  {
    "Question": "New Mexico",
    "Answer": "Santa Fe"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Arizona",
    "Answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Utah",
    "Answer": "Salt Lake City"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Idaho",
    "Answer": "Boise"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Washington",
    "Answer": "Olympia"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Oregon",
    "Answer": "Salem"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Nevada",
    "Answer": "Carson City"
  },
  {
    "Question": "California",
    "Answer": "Sacramento"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hawaii",
    "Answer": "Honolulu"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Alaska",
    "Answer": "Juneau"
  }
]